<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OnTracker</string>
    <string name="home">home</string>
    <string name="add_category">add_category</string>
    <string name="list_category">list_category</string>
    <string name="profile">profile</string>
    <string name="logout">logout</string>
    <string name="location">Item location</string>
    <string name="Description">Item Description</string>
    <string name="facebook_application_id" translatable="false">3005369646362240</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb3005369646362240</string>
    <string name="ask_question_title">Have a Quesiton?</string>
    <string name="QAForum_header"><![CDATA[Q&A Forum]]></string>
    <string name="display_questions_header">All Questions</string>
    <string name="terms"> This Application is owned and operated by OnTracker. The use of this Application and the content and information available on this application (collectively the Services) shall be subject to acceptance of and compliance with the terms and conditions set forth in these terms of use (collectively, the Terms of Us) and elsewhere on this application. The terms you, your, yours, member members and yourself refer to all visitors/members to this application. Your agreement to comply with and be bound by these Terms of Use is deemed to occur upon your first use of the application. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you should not review information or obtain goods, services, or products from this application. The Sample Store has the total right to edit or delete any content in the Application, including this Agreement, without notifying you. USE OF THIS APPLICATION You agree not to:- (a) reproduce, copy, distribute, modify, publish, transmit, display, use, reuse, re-publicize, assign, sublicense, sell, or exploit for any public or commercial purpose, any portion of the application, use of the application, or access to the Application. (b) attempt to change, add to, remove, deface, hack or otherwise interfere with this Application or any material or content displayed on this Application; and/or ©️ access or use this Application in any way that could or is intended to damage or impair the Application, or any server or network underlying the Application, or interfere with anyone else\'s use and enjoyment of the Application. USE OF INFORMATION We have a group privacy policy which sets out how we handle personal data that you may provide or that we may collect, in connection with your access or use of this application. The policy is available on this application. You accept and agree to the terms set out in the policy and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data in accordance with the policy. SUBMISSIONS You may post reviews of products or services, comments, suggestions, or other messages (collectively referred to as “Submissions”) so long as the content of your Submission is not unlawful, threatening, abusive, spiteful, defamatory, invasive of privacy, obscene, profane, sexually explicit, fraudulent or otherwise objectionable or injurious to third parties (including, but not limited to, any content that encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate applicable law). You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of your Submission. The Sample Store reserves the right (but not the obligation) to monitor, edit and remove any Submission. By posting or sending us any Submission, you grant The Sample Store a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such Submission in any media. PROMOTIONS From time to time, we may offer and/or co-sponsor contests and games on the Application. Each of these activities shall be governed by specific rules accessible from the Application. DISCLAIMER AND EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY 1. This Application, the Services, the information on this Application and use of all related facilities are provided on an as is, as available basis without any warranties whether express or implied. 2. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we disclaim all representations and warranties relating to this Application and its contents, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this Application, warranties of merchantability, quality, fitness for a particular purpose, accuracy, availability, noninfringement or implied warranties from course of dealing or usage of trade. 3. We do not warrant that this Application will always be accessible, uninterrupted, timely, secure, error free or free from computer virus or other invasive or damaging code or that this Application will not be affected by any Acts of God or other force majeure events, including inability to obtain or shortage of necessary materials, equipment facilities, power or telecommunications, lack of telecommunications equipment or facilities and failure of information technology or telecommunications equipment or facilities. 4. While we may use reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this Application, we make no warranties or representations as to its accuracy, timeliness, or completeness. WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, HOWSOEVER CAUSED, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE, RELIANCE ON OR DOWNLOADING FROM THE APPLICATION, OR ANY DELAYS, INACCURACIES IN THE INFORMATION OR IN ITS TRANSMISSION INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS OR PROFITS, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 5. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer that cannot be excluded or limited are affected. 6. Notwithstanding our efforts to ensure that our Application/system is secure, you acknowledge that all electronic data transfers are potentially susceptible to interception by others. We cannot, and do not, warrant that data transfers pursuant to this Application, or electronic mail transmitted to and from us, will not be monitored or read by others. 7. Although we use reasonable endeavours to ensure that any software made available on this Application is suitable for downloading, installation and use by you, all such software is provided as is without any warranty. Specifically, and without limitation, we do not warrant that any such software is virus free, without defects, compatible with other software or operating systems or suitable for any specific purpose. We accept no liability for any loss or damage caused by the downloading, installation or use of any such software, and the general exclusions and limitations above apply to such downloading, installation or use by you. LINKS TO THIS APPLICATION You may not create a link to any page of this Application without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this Application, you do so at your own risk and these Terms of Use will apply to your use of this Application by linking to it. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS AND LINKS TO THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS The Sample Store may display advertisements from third parties, such as banner advertisements and pop-up texts, and links to third party applications, on the Application. We are not responsible for the content of such advertisements or links, any products, services, or other materials relating to such advertisements, any linked application, or any link contained in a linked application. The display of any such advertisement or link does not imply endorsement by The Sample Store of the advertisement or linked application or any content therein. IN NO EVENT WILL THE SAMPLE STORE BE LIABLE, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, TO ANYONE FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO ANY USE, CONTINUED USE OR RELIANCE ON ANY THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENT DISPLAYED ON THE APPLICATION, ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES OR OTHER MATERIALS RELATING TO ANY SUCH ADVERTISEMENT, ANY LINKED THIRD PARTY APPLICATION OR ANY LINK CONTAINED IN A LINKED APPLICATION. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS All editorial content, information, photographs, illustrations, artwork and other graphic materials, and names, logos and trade marks on this Application are protected by copyright laws and/or other laws and/or international treaties, and belong to us and/or our suppliers, as the case may be. These works, logos, graphics, sounds or images may not be copied, reproduced, retransmitted, distributed, disseminated, sold, published, broadcasted or circulated whether in whole or in part, unless expressly permitted by us and/or our suppliers, as the case may be. Nothing contained on the Application should be construed as granting by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark displayed on the Application without our written permission. Misuse of any trademarks or any other content displayed on the Application is prohibited. We will not hesitate to take legal action against any unauthorised usage of its trade marks, name or symbols to preserve and protect its rights in the matter. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. Other product and company names mentioned herein may also be the trade marks of their respective owners. CHANGES TO TERMS OF USE These Terms of Use may be modified from time to time. Any modifications to these Terms of Use will be effective upon posting. You should therefore read these Terms of Use before you place any order. Your continued use of the Application after any modifications to the Terms of Use indicates your acceptance of the modified Terms of Use GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION. This Application may be accessed from all countries around the world where the local technology permits. As each country has differing laws, by accessing this Application both we and you agree that the laws of the Republic of Singapore, without regard to the conflict of laws principles thereof, will apply to all matters relating to these Terms of Use. You accept and agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the Republic of Singapore in respect of any dispute or difference arising out of and/or in connection with these Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="privacy"> ONTARCKER GROUP PRIVACY POLICY
    This is the Privacy Policy (“Policy”) of OnTracker and its subsidiaries (collectively the “OnTracker Group”).
    You have been directed to this Policy because a company within the OnTracker Group is collecting, using, or disclosing your personal data.
    In this Policy, when we use “we”, “us” or “our”, we refer to the company (within the OnTarcker Group) which is collecting your personal data, or which is operating the application which you are accessing or using.
    This Policy applies to all personal data that you may provide to us and the personal data we hold about you. By providing us with your personal data or by accessing, using or viewing the applicable application or any of its services, functions or contents (including transmitting, caching or storing of any such personal data), you shall be deemed to have agreed to each and all the terms, conditions, and notices in this Policy. If you do not agree, please cease use of the relevant application(s) and/or service(s) and DO NOT provide any personal data to us.
    1. WHAT PERSONAL DATA IS COLLECTED
    1.1 When you use our application, any service we provide or in your interaction with us, the personal data we may collect includes:-
    (a) Data collected directly from you. This may be done through this application, over the phone, by email, or in person when you meet our staff or representatives. The data collected may include, but is not limited to:
    • your contact information, including your (first and last) name, (billing and/or delivery) address, birthdate and email address and, optionally, your telephone number. We need your e-mail address and (optionally) telephone number so that we may contact you if we have questions or information for you regarding your order or the service that we are providing or will provide to you;
    • other information required to be able to process your order or to provide you with the service, such as information concerning the products you have ordered or the service we are providing to you, the billing and/or delivery address, banking and/or credit card details;
    • if you have created an online profile or account, the preferences and interests stored in such profile or account (please see below for further information concerning the profiles); and
    • if you have contacted customer service, the details of this contact and the contact history.
    (b) Data collected by automated means. Various technologies may be used on our application and our mobile and web-based applications in order to make them more user-friendly, effective and secure. Such technologies may lead to data being collected automatically by us or by third parties on behalf of us. This data does not generally, but may, contain a user’s personal data. Examples of such technologies include:
    • Click-stream data. A visit to one of our applications results in data that is transmitted from your browser to our server being automatically collected and stored by us or by third parties on behalf of us. This data can include, in particular, the following:
    - the visitor’s IP address
    - the date and time of the visit
    - the referral URL (the application from which the visitor has come)
    - the pages visited on our application
    - information about the browser used (browser type and version, operating system, etc).
    • Cookies. A number of places on our application and our mobile and web-based applications make use of cookies. These are essentially small text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive or your user device by your web browser. We can use cookies to identify the owner of a user account and to store articles in a shopping basket during the purchasing process. In other words, cookies help to make our application or our (mobile and web-based) applications more user-friendly, more effective and more secure. The cookies usually used by us are so-called “session cookies”, which are automatically deleted at the end of the visit to the relevant application. By default, web browsers enable the use of cookies but this function can also be disabled. However, this will result in some services not being available. It is also possible to manually delete cookies after their use via the web browser. More information may be available from your web browser provider. OnTracker Group Privacy Policy (Draft 10 June 2014)_1
    • Flash cookies. A particular form of cookie is the flash cookie. In contrast to normal cookies, these cookies are not created and saved by the web browser but are governed by the Adobe Flash plug-in. These can contain more information than normal cookies and cannot be deleted or disabled via the browser; this is only possible if you follow instructions available from the Adobe Flash Player application. You can also obtain more information about these cookies on that application.
    • Web beacons and tracking links. Web beacons (also known as pixel tags and clear GIFs) involve graphics that are not apparent to the user. Tracking links and/or similar technologies consist of a few lines of programming code and can be embedded in our application or our (mobile) applications. In conjunction with cookies, these are primarily used for statistical analysis purposes. This technology can also be used for tracking traffic patterns on applications, as well as finding out if an e-mail has been received and opened and to see if there has been any response.
    • Web analytics. Web analytics is the term given to a method for collecting and assessing the behaviour of visitors to applications and (mobile) applications. This includes the analysis of traffic patterns in order, for example, to determine the frequency of visits to certain parts of a application or (mobile) application, or to find out what information and services our visitors are most interested in. For these purposes, we primarily make use of click-stream data and the other techniques listed above. Web analytics are carried out by Google Analytics and/or other selected parties. You can find out more information about the processing of web analytics data by Google Analytics in paragraph 7 below.
    2. HOW IS THE COLLECTED PERSONAL DATA USED
    2.1 We use your personal data for the purposes of serving you. This includes, where applicable:-
    • providing you with the products and services that you have requested e.g. notifying you regarding the status of your order or delivery, assessment of your creditworthiness (for which we may use third parties);
    • ensuring that your transactions on our applications are safe and secure;
    • providing you with a convenient shopping experience;
    • contacting you for feedback after a sale of a product or service; and
    • resolving any problems or disputes you may encounter in relation to our products and services.
    2.2 We may also use your personal data for purposes connected or relevant to the business of the OnTracker Group, such as:-
    • complying with legal and regulatory obligations and requirements;
    • enforcing obligations owed to the OnTracker Group;
    • researching and developing new products and services or improving existing products and services of the OnTracker Group;
    • accounting, risk management, compliance and record keeping purposes;
    • carrying out research, planning and statistical analysis; and
    • staff training.
    2.3 Your personal data may also be anonymised for use by the OnTracker Group for other purposes.
    2.4 If you have consented, your personal data may be used by the OnTracker Group for the purposes of marketing products and services offered on the application or other products or services offered by the OnTracker Group or those of its strategic partners or business affiliates e.g. informing you of latest activities, special offers, promotions or sending you newsletters.
    2.5 In order for us to market products and services which are of special interest and relevance to you, we may analyse and rely on your overall interaction with us (such as but not limited to your shopping behaviour in e-shops, your use of loyalty programmes, your ratings and reviews of products, your contact history with our customer service, your newsletter clicks/ opening results, your surfing behaviour (web tracking), the newsletter types you are subscribed to, your participation in promotions or events, your interactions with us and your use of (mobile) applications).
    2.5 If you have contacted us with any complaints, feedback, comments, suggestions, we will use and disclose your personal data (including your contact history) to respond to you and provide you with the best service possible. If you are the complainant and you do not want us to disclose your identity to the party you are complaining about, you must let us know immediately. However, it may not always be possible to handle your complaint on the basis of anonymity.
    2.6 When using your personal data to contact you for the above purposes, we may contact you via regular mail, fax, e-mail, SMS, telephone or any other electronic means.
    2.7 If we need to use your personal data for any other purposes, we will notify you and obtain your consent beforehand. You will be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for the use of your personal data for these other purposes.
    3. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
    3.1 We will not sell your personal data to third parties.
    3.2 We will only disclose your personal data to third parties where you have provided us consent, and in the situations expressly set out in in this Policy. If you have consented to receiving marketing information from us, our strategic partners and business associates, we will be disclosing your personal data to them.
    3.3 Your personal data may be disclosed and shared within the OnTracker Group to allow us to provide the products and services which you have requested.
    3.4 We may disclose or share your personal data with third parties (including other companies within the OnTracker Group) who provide necessary services to us, such as:-
    • service providers and data processors working on our behalf and providing services such as hosting and maintenance services, analysis services, e-mail messaging services, delivery services, handling of payment transactions, solvency check and address check, etc; and
    • our consultants and professional advisers (such as accountants, lawyers, auditors).
    3.5 We will also disclose your personal data to third parties in order to comply with legal obligations or industry requirements. This includes disclosures to legal, regulatory, governmental, tax and law enforcement authorities.
    3.6 Our application may have the functionalities to allow you to share your personal data with other third parties such as other users of our application. You are responsible for your choice(s) and are deemed to have provided consent for any sharing of your personal data in the manner provided by the application.
    3.7 You fully understand and consent that we may transfer your personal data to any location outside of Canada for the purposes set out in this paragraph 3. When transferring your personal data outside of Canada we will protect your personal data to a standard comparable to the protection accorded to your personal data under the Canada Personal Data Protection Act 2012 by ensuring that the recipient is either in a jurisdiction which has comparable data protection laws, or is contractually bound to protect your personal data.
</string>
    <string name="add_question">Add Question</string>
    <string name="list_questions">List of All Questions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
</resources>